### Hi! I'm Ilaria Olimpia Posca, a front-end developer who

loves = ["languages", "photography", "cultural
heritage"];

Resume

Name & Surname

e & Surname Date of Birth

Ilaria Olimpia Posca

August 21st, 1986 viale Faenza 27 – 20142 Milan, Italy

Address Telephone

+39 373 8655086 ilaria.posca@gmail.com

E-Mail **Portfolio** & Linkedin

it.linkedin.com/in/ilariaolimpia-posca

https://www.ilariaolimpiaposca.com/

Self presentation

I'm Ilaria a 34 years old <u>passionate</u> and <u>accurate</u> front-end developer with an eagle-eye that comes from my passion for photography. This gives me a good knowledge of all Adobe products such as Illustrator and Photoshop and also of their Gnu-alternatives.

During the last year I have worked with companies such as: Sky DE (CRM) Danone(Gallia), Limina, Acea, Alfaparf, Cariboni, Fai Service, Villa Flaminia, Generali, OZ Racing, Rheingold, Ritrama, La Roche Posay, Treccani.

### Competences

- Most common web platforms such as:
   Adobe Experience Manager, Liferay, WordPress, Joomla, Oracle Siebel CRM;
- HTML & CSS (and its *preprocessors/framework* such as SASS, LESS, Foundation, Bootstrap)
- Vanilla Javascript (Ecmascript 5/6) and its framework: JQuery, VueJS, React(and basic concept of states management) and AngularJS(basic knowledge);
- Good knowledge in most common *agile development* resource: Jira, Confluence, BitBucket, Bamboo, Git;
- Good knowledge of Unix Systems and DOS;
- Basic PHP
- Good knowledge of tools such as *task runner* (Grunt), *Toolkit* (Gulp) and *package manager* (NPM, Bower, Yarn);
- Basic knowledge of deployment platforms (Docker and Jenkins)

#### Languages

Italian	Mother tongue
English	C1
Swedish	C1
Norwegian	B2
French	B1
Spanish	A2
Dutch	A2

Russian A2

# Work experiences

Nov 2020 - Jan 2021 Jan 2020 - Aug 2020	Application Developer at Btwin-Invetsech-Blue Application Developer at Accenture - Investech-Blue Development of Oracle Siebel CRM
October 2019 - Nov 2019	Web-Developer at <i>LiminaRivista</i> - Freelance Development of a custom theme for a Web-magazine based on <i>Wordpress</i>
July 2019 - Nov 2019	Junior Front-end Developer at Accenture - Investech-Blue Development on Enterprise CMS
October 2018 - June 2019	Junior Front-end developer at <i>Doing</i> part of Capgemini, Milan Development of Corporate Websites
June 2018 - Sept. 2018	Internship Front-end developer at Filmmaster's web agency <i>Gag</i> , Milan Custom DEM and GDPR pages
June 2012 - Sept. 2017	Freelance Swedish interpreter & translator: Milan, Rotterdam, Bergamo.
September 2012 - June 2014	Mother tongue teacher at Medbrogareskolan, Göteborg
April 2010 - Jan. 2012	Content Manager & Photo editor at Folkuniveritetet, Göteborg  Awarded in 2012 as Best Educational Website at Swedish Web Awards
November 2010 - Sept. 2011	Corporate Media Manager at <i>ClaireDK</i> , Mölndal
2009 - 2010	Photo reporter at GötebrogsPosten, Göteborg  Photo graphs on at Sound in a França site young talenta intentional Milan
September 2009	Photographer at Sound in a Frame six young talents intertwined, Milan Post-Production & Assistant at Pink Turtle, Milan
March 2008 - Sept. 2009	
September 2004 - June 2005	Internship Digital Archivist at Fondazione A.Ratti, Como

# Education and training Schools & Diplomas

	Advanced Oracle API Javascript at Oracle University, Milan
April 2020	Adobe Experience Manager at NTT Data, Rome
January 2019	Front-end Developer at Manpower Formazione, Milan
March 2018 - June 2018	Search Engine Optimization at InfoMediaTech AB, Göteborg
January 2012 - June 2012	Literary Composition (Litterär Gestaltning) at Folkuniversitetet, Göteborg
September 2012 - June 2012	Thesis on: The Scandinavian Utopia (Den Skandinaviska Utopi) marks 4/5
	Highschool Diploma Swedish A&B at Folkuniversitetet, Göteborg
September 2010 - Sept. 2012	Thesis on: Swedish Camera development from Early years to Hasselblad (Svenska kamera
	tillverking från hålkameror till måne) marks 4/5
	Member of the Student's Council and Class President
	Bachelor Degree in <i>Photography</i> at Istituto Europeo di Design, Milan
September 2006 - July 2009	Visual Art department marks 95/100
	Philosophy at Università Statale di Milano, Milan
September 2005 - July 2006	Diploma Leonardo Project at Liceo Artistico Caravaggio, Milan
September 2000 - July 2005	Thesis on: Freud & Jung: How the advent of psychoanalysis changed art marks 80/100